nice to meet you.
初めまして
It's cute.
かわいいですね
sometimes.
たまに
It's not every once in a while, right?
たまにじゃないでしょ
It's said a lot.
結構言われます
Are you popular?
モテます?
Well, I wasn't very popular.
あんま、モテなかったですね
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏いるんですか?
I'm not there.
いないです
Isn't there?
いないですか?
How many years have you been gone?
何年くらいいないですか?
How much?
どれくらい?
I've been here for about a year and a half.
1年半くらいいます
Oh, there aren't that many?
あ、そんなにいないですか?
That's surprising.
意外ですね
About 2 people, about 3 people, a lot.
2人くらい、3人くらい、すごく
What type of man is he?
どういう男性がタイプなの?
It's easy to find someone who can lead you.
リードしてくれる人とか、 や さしい、
A type is a person who has different types.
方 々がある人がタイプです
I see.
なるほど
A kind and kind person.
優しくて、方々がある人
If I'm wrong, I'm older.
間違ったら、年上とか
I agree.
そうですね
I like older people.
年上が好きです
How old is old?
年上って、何歳くらいまで?
Until about 30 years old.
30歳くらいまで
Ah, I think you can go pretty high, right?
あ、結構上いけるんじゃないですか?
That's pretty high.
結構上ですね
That's good.
いいっすね
It took a little courage.
ちょっと勇気出ましたね
In terms of appearance?
見た目で言うと?
What does it look like?
見た目?
Be honest.
正直で
Isn't he really handsome?
め ちゃめちゃイケメンじゃないですか?
Don't you eat noodles?
めん食いない?
Which one?
どっちかって言うと
No, I don't know.
いや、どうだろう
Well, maybe so.
まあ、そうかもしれないです
I guess you could say he's dog-like, like Ryo Yoshizawari?
よしざわりょうみたいな、 犬系って言うのかな?
I agree.
そうですね
There are many dogs, and they seem to be older than me.
犬系で、方々があって、 年上みたいですよ
What is your ex-boyfriend like?
前の彼氏は、どんな感じ?
My previous boyfriend was
前の彼氏は、
Well, well, there was no tolerance.
あ んま、 あ ん ま、 包容力なかった
So, you don't have a boyfriend or anything right now?
じゃあ、今、 いないですよね、彼氏とか
If you had a boyfriend, where would you like to go?
もし彼氏できたら、 どこ行きたいですか?
I want to go to the sea.
海とか行きたいですね
sea?
海?
That's good.
いいっすね
Do you like the sea?
海好きなの?
That kind of openness.
そういう、 開放で
It's like a private ocean.
なんか、プライベート海みたいな
A stylish space for just the two of us.
おしゃれな、2人だけの空間で
That's what I mean.
ってことね
That's good.
いいっすね
Well, the story is about to change drastically.
まあ、ガッツリ話変わるんですけど
It suits you.
似合ってるよね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Is this active?
これ、現役ですか?
I think it's going to get a little bit interesting.
ちょっと、 ちょっと、面白くなってそう
Isn't it a bit see-through?
ちょっと、透けてないですか?
Only forever.
ずっとだけ
It kind of looks like white polka dots.
なんか、白の水玉みたいな、 感じのね
Do you have any hobbies?
趣味とかあるんですか?
My hobby is playing games.
趣味は、 ゲームですね
game?
ゲーム?
Hobbies, etc.
趣味とか
What games do you like?
何のゲームが好きなの?
A long time ago, a little while ago, there was something like Wilderness Code.
昔、 ちょっと昔なんですけど、 荒野コードとか
Oh, it's not SBF, is it?
ああ、 SBFじゃないんじゃないの?
I mean, that kind of game.
なんていうか、 ああいうゲームって
I mean, I don't know, but with PS4 and stuff like that,
なんていうか、 なんか、でもPS4とか で、
We did that, and now we have a mobile version.
やったり、 あとは、 今はモバイル版とか で、
I often use my cell phone.
携帯でよく やってます
So, there's something.
じゃあ、何かあるんですね
Does it feel like online?
オンライン的な感じ?
Not three or anything, I don't know, but
スリーとかじゃなくて、 わかんないけど、
Do you like online games?
オンラインゲームは好きですか?
I agree.
そうですね
I like it.
好きです
Is it pretty strong?
結構強いですか?
No, it's not that strong.
いや、あんま強くない
Do you want to participate in sports events?
体育会とか出たいとこないですか?
Well, I guess it does.
えー、なんかまあ、 ありますね
Are you coming out?
出るの?
I almost want to go out.
出たいなーぐらい
Are you getting stronger?
もっと強くなってやってる?
that's right.
そうです
Other than that, what about mobile games?
それ以外は、携帯ゲームとか?
I'm interested too.
僕も興味あるんで
I like games.
ゲーム好きなんで
Please try a little more and let me know.
もうちょっとやって教えてください
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Well, it's about time, just for a little while.
じゃあ、そろそろね、 ちょっとだけ、
I would like to ask some naughty questions.
えっちめんな質問を していきたいと思います
If anything,
どちらかというと、
The neck and chest are raw liver.
あ ちくびとくりが 生肝体なの
Which one?
どっちの?
Well, both.
えー、どちらもですね
I see.
なるほど
Do you masturbate?
オナニーとかする?
I don't do it much.
あんまりしない
Not much?
あんまりしない?
I don't think so.
しないですね
Do you not do it much?
あんまりしないですか?
I see.
なるほど
So, what kind of sex do you like?
じゃあ、どういう えっちが好きですか?
I want to do something a little different, like normal sex.
なんか普通のセックスとか、 ちょっと変わった ことがしたいよ
Or something.
とか
No, but normal.
いや、 でもノーマル
normal?
ノーマル?
Sex like normal flirting.
普通のいちゃいちゃみたいなセックス
I agree.
そうですね
Now, Mr. Yoshida wants to do something like a dormitory.
それを、 今、吉田さんが寮みたいな ことをしたいと
Well then, it feels like you're meeting me today.
じゃあ、今日僕とね、 会えてる感じになりますけど、
People say that Yoshida-san looks a lot like a dormitory.
結 構吉田さんが寮に似てるって言われるんですよ
yes.
はい
I'm playing a little bit.
ちょっと弾いてますね
I'm going there now, so can you judge if we look alike?
僕今行くんで、 似てるか判断してもらっていいですか?
It's quite independent.
結構自主だよ
How many.
多少
How many?
多少?
There's not much resemblance.
あんまり似てないです
I wonder if there's a little bit in it?
ちょっとぐらいの入ってるかな?
It's not very similar.
ちょっと あんまり似てないです
got it.
わかりました
You're doing it normally.
普通にやってるね
It's a bushy bisu, isn't it?
ふさやびすでしょ
Do it yourself?
自分でやる?
No, do it yourself
いや、自分でや
I will.
ります
Doesn't it hurt a lot?
め っちゃ痛みない?
No, it doesn't hurt that much.
いや、あんまり痛くない
Isn't this one wearing a shirt?
これ何かシャツ着てない?
I don't wear it.
着ないです
Don't you wear it?
着ないの?
Are you in this?
この中ですか?
It's transparent.
透けちゃってる
I don't wear it much.
あんまり着ないです
Can't you see anything?
なんか見られない?
Can't see it?
見られない?
You might be seen.
見られてるかもしれない
It'll be out for a year.
一年間出るよね
I felt embarrassed at that time.
その時恥ずかしい
I feel like I'm being watched.
ちょっとなんか見られてるみたい
I agree.
そうですね
My hair is also loose.
髪もさらさらしてる
Jellofin.
ジェロフィン
How long?
いつぐらい?
English junior high school is over.
英中学校終わりです
Ah, I see.
あ、そうか
Rapid growth.
急成長って
Cut yourself with your finger.
自分にさ、指で切る
bean paste
あ ん
No need.
ず いかん
behind the hair.
髪の後ろ
Waist.
腰
face.
顔
I'll squat down here.
ここに下にしゃがるよ
Can I come in?
入 れていい?
Yeah.
うん
If you move.
動けば
Attracted.
引きついて
Please move it a little.
ちょっと動かしてください
Oh yeah, move it.
そうそう、動かしてください